<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <title>Tofutush&#39;s blog</title>
  <subtitle>Where I write stuff once in a blue moon</subtitle>
  <link href="https://tofutush.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" />
  <link href="https://tofutush.github.io/" />
  <updated>2024-09-29T00:00:00Z</updated>
  <id>https://tofutush.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name>Tofutush</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>Resurrecting Old Ideas and Magic Academies</title>
    <link href="https://tofutush.github.io/posts/resurrecting-old-ideas-and-magic-academies.html" />
    <updated>2024-09-29T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://tofutush.github.io/posts/resurrecting-old-ideas-and-magic-academies.html</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;(This is a post from Cohost, reposted here.)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I had an idea in middle school of a comic featuring people who naturally look like Homestuck god-tiers who are attending to a school on a mountain. It was never finished -- hardly even started -- but if I don&#39;t talk about it here it&#39;s going to die in my head forever.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, it&#39;s been a while and I&#39;ve forgotten most stuff, and the original notebook I drew the thing on was probably lost after we moved, but here:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The people are all Homestuck-white and have Homestuck-god wings, wearing Homestuck-god hoodies. Each with a unique wing / eye / text-color, which turned into &amp;quot;accent colors&amp;quot; in TIR.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each person has a &amp;quot;partner,&amp;quot; and can&#39;t sleep unless the partner is awake, and can&#39;t wake up unless the partner is asleep. Yes, like dream-selves. You can already see how similar this is to Homestuck. Except the &amp;quot;partner&amp;quot; is someone else that actually exists as an independent person.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the school part, it is more like a college despite being called a middle school, and instead of choosing a major, the school assigns one to you based on what they think you&#39;ll do best in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our protagonist, Ribbon, got into &amp;quot;News.&amp;quot; Her friend Eva got into &amp;quot;Detective.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now you&#39;re seeing parallels to TIR: two most important things in Hillslope are the press and Sparky&#39;s investigation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Two characters, Ribbon and Sky, are originally created here. (At least, the accent colors and Chinese names are the same.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The story would involve a mystery of a thief and how Eva and Ribbon solve it, Eva using her detective skills and Ribbon using the Power of Propaganda&lt;sup&gt;tm&lt;/sup&gt; since her class runs the school newspaper.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, I don&#39;t ever plan on resurrecting this comic, but I do reuse some aspects of it, like the thief plot, Ribbon and Sky, and the school-in-a-mountain. Qibli is to be attending a magic academy in a mountain.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Second Post</title>
    <link href="https://tofutush.github.io/posts/second-post.html" />
    <updated>2024-09-26T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://tofutush.github.io/posts/second-post.html</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I am wasting my life on stupid shit.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>About me</title>
    <link href="https://tofutush.github.io/posts/about-me.html" />
    <updated>2024-09-24T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://tofutush.github.io/posts/about-me.html</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hi. Tofutush here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IDK why I started a blog. I&#39;m not a writer. But I just figured I wanted to do something about this site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yeesh I ran out of things to say pretty quickly. How about I tell you about my name, Tofutush. It&#39;s a silly name from Captain Underpants. Wow how old am I.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I like comics and my OCs. Look at them &lt;a href=&quot;https://tofutush.github.io/The-Iron-Ragdoll&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I gotta put a link to every site I&#39;m on. Not a lot, mind you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://toyhou.se/Tofutush&quot;&gt;Toyhouse&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://artfight.net/~Tofutush&quot;&gt;Artfight&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Discord (tofutush)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I used to go on Cohost. But then it shut down. This site&#39;s color scheme is taken from there.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
</feed>